(gasps)
This place is great!
(Leonard:)So nice of that doctor
to just let you use it.
(Penny:)Well, she is taking me
to an Indigo Girls concert,
(Penny:)so hold that thought.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)Well,
should we check
each other for ticks?
(Amy:)Sheldon, all we did
was walk in from the car.
(Howard:)Oh. Well,
suit yourself.
(Sheldon:)Who wants to check me?
(Amy:)On the other hand, safety first.
(rain falling loudly)
(Amy:)Wow, it's really
coming down.
(Penny:)This sucks.
(Leonard:)And there goes our hike.
Oh, not our hike!
(Sheldon:)Now we have
(Sheldon:)to stay safe and warm.
(Penny:)You know, we could still go.
(Penny:)A little rain
isn't gonna kill us.
(Leonard:)Have you been outside
in the rain with Sheldon?